Kessie LEUNG

☑ hl.kessieleung@gmail.com

in khlleung

hlleung74.github.io/portfolio-website/

Summary

Highly motivated and collaborative professional with a year of experience as a Creative Communications Assistant and a passion for social media content creation. As a versatile team player, she is always ready to accept new challenges and adapt to different work cultures.

Employment History

Creative Communications Assistant at 1a space

JUL 2023 - JUL 2024

- Collaborated with cross-functional teams to plan content publishing schedules for social media platforms, including Instagram, Facebook and YouTube, ensuring timely and engaging content delivery.
- Planned, shot, and edited 15+ interview and promotional videos for social media platforms that are visually engaging.
- Shot and retouched event photos, with 30+ photos featured on the company's social media channels.

IT Intern at Hong Kong Housing Society

JUL 2020 - JUN 2021

- Handled 90% of 20+ security awareness training material creation, including video motion graphics and comic strips, improving internal staff's skills in spotting online scams.
- Troubleshooted 40+ users' inquiries, facilitating workflow by providing user-friendly guidance.

Education

2022 - 2023	MA in Creative Media – City University of Hong Kong.
2018 - 2022	BSc in Computer Science – City University of Hong Kong.
Spring 2020	Semester Exchange – University of Liverpool (Liverpool, UK).

Skills

Multimedia Production: Adobe Creative Suite (After Effects, Audition, Illustrator, Photoshop,

Premiere Pro), DaVinci Resolve, Final Cut Pro, Canva.

Web Development: WIX, WordPress, HTML, CSS, JavaScript.

Computer Skills: MS Office, Google Suite, Mailchimp.

Hard Skills: Video Production, Video Editing, Video Shooting, Motion Graphics,

Photo Shooting, Marketing.

Soft Skills: Attention to Detail, Collaboration, Creative, Critical Thinking, Time

Management.

Languages

Cantonese (Native), English (Fluent), Mandarin (Intermediate).